Your dietician and nutritionist here to help us out because we don't know if this all is true or not.
Netta Mays.
Where do you work?
I work for myself. I have a private practice. I take insurance. It's called Nutrition by Netta.
Oh! Nutrition by Netta.
Yes. Thank you.
All right. I guess you start with raw carrots.
Yes. So let's cook. Let's get into it. I have a raw carrot salad. We have these beautiful carrot ribbons, just like you saw on TikTok.
And you made the ribbons just with one of these peelers.
Yes. If you saw during the little clip, we peeled the carrots to make the ribbons.
Okay.
You don't need too much equipment. That's it. We try to make it simple. I don't like people to buy too much stuff.
What did you just put in there?
So this is cilantro.
Okay.
So there's two types of people, people who hate cilantro or people who love cilantro.
I love cilantro.
We have these roasted black and white sesame seeds. Roasting really helps to bring out delicious flavor, highlighting the natural flavor in the foods.
Then we have our vinaigrette. So this is soy sauce, lemon juice. We have some sesame oil, which also goes with the roasted sesame seeds.
I'm going to give it a little blend.
Well, this is going to make it tasty.
Oh, this is, it tastes delicious. It really does. It tastes delicious.
As far as all of the health benefits that they're claiming of this salad, I would never recommend any food as a cure-all.
But I would say that this is a great thing to add to your day and your regimen.
Okay.
Right?
Because, yeah, it promises a lot of things.
Yeah, I think it's a little...
So, yeah.
I love you.
So...
Yeah.
So, yeah.